<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Language Name="Chinese (Mainland)">
	<s>SEconomy初始化失败:</s>
	<s>SEconomy:所有玩家共计有{0}。</s>
	<s>blah</s>
	<!-- SEconomyPlugin.cs: 4-14 -->
	<s></s>
	<s> * http://plugins.tw.id.au</s>
	<s> * /sec[onomy] reload|rl - 重载SEconomy</s>
	<s> * /sec[onomy] stop - 关闭SEconomy</s>
	<s> * /sec[onomy] start - 开启SEconomy</s>
	<s>SEconomy 已加载。</s>
	<s>seconomy 已停止。输入/sec start 重新开启。</s>
	<s>SEconomy 已停止。</s>
	<s>seconomy 已开启。输入/sec stop 关闭。</s>
	<s>SEconomy 加载失败, 在本次会话中将不可用。</s>
	<s>SEconomy 已开启。</s>
	<!-- EventHandlers.cs: 15-28 -->
	<s>你击杀了{0}，获得了{1}。</s>
	<s>{0}击杀了你，你失去了{1}。</s>
	<s>你{3}{0}，目标{1}。交易ID {2}</s>
	<s>The server</s>
	<s>转账</s>
	<s>收到转账</s>
	<s>你{0}{1}{2}</s>
	<s>支出</s>
	<s>收到</s>
	<s>失去</s>
	<s>获得</s>
	<s>，因</s>
	<s>你现在拥有{0}。</s>
	<s>seconomy async: error occurred on a task thread: </s>
	<!-- ChatCommands.cs: 29-59 -->
	<s>本服务器正在使用{0}</s>
	<s>下载地址: http://plugins.tw.id.au 汉化:群190534564</s>
	<s>你可以:</s>
	<s>* 输入/bank bal查看你的存款.</s>
	<s>* 输入/bank pay [玩家名] [数额] 和别的玩家进行交易</s>
	<s>* 输入/bank bal [玩家名] 查看他人的存款.</s>
	<s>* 输入/bank give|take [玩家名] [数额] 增加或减少他人的存款.</s>
	<s>* 在后台输入/bank mgr开启管理界面.</s>
	<s>* 输入/bank savejournal保存日志.</s>
	<s>* 输入/bank loadjournal加载日志.</s>
	<s>* 输入/bank squashjournal压缩日志.</s>
	<s>[SEconomy]已重置{0}的账户.</s>
	<s>[SEconomy]重置完毕.</s>
	<s>[SEconomy]找不到玩家\"{0}\"的账户.</s>
	<s>[SEconomy]你没有执行此操作的权限.</s>
	<s>[SEconomy]你的账户已被停用.</s>
	<s>[SEconomy]存款:{0} {1}</s>
	<s>(已停用)</s>
	<s>[SEconomy]找不到该玩家的账户.</s>
	<s>[SEconomy]打开管理界面.</s>
	<s>[SEconomy]管理界面异常退出:</s>
	<s>[SEconomy]管理界面已关闭.</s>
	<s>[SEconomy]只有后台可以使用管理界面.</s>
	<s>[SEconomy]正在备份交易记录.</s>
	<s>[SEconomy]正在加载交易记录.</s>
	<s>[SEconomy]你没有权限压缩交易记录.</s>
	<s>[SEconomy]找不到玩家{0}.</s>
	<s>[SEconomy]\"{0}\"不是一个合适的数额.</s>
	<s>[SEconomy]用法: /bank pay [玩家名] [数额]</s>
	<s>[SEconomy]你没有权限执行此操作.</s>
	<s>[SEconomy]用法: /bank give|take [玩家] [数额]</s>
	<s>[SEconomy]你没有权限执行此操作.</s>
	<!-- XmlTransactionJournal.cs: 60-84 -->
	<s>世界{0}的世界账户已停用. 货币系统已停止工作.</s>
	<s>世界账户加载时出现错误. 货币系统已停止工作.</s>
	<s>
		这是SEconomy交易记录文件。

		你现在应该能看出来这是XML格式的。这个文件储存着服务器中所有的支出和收入。
		这个文件并不是时刻被写入的，所有的交易都在内存中完成，并仅在备份时被写入
		到这个文件中。

		修改这个文件并不能修改账户余额，因为你还需要执行/bank loadjournal 命令使
		使其生效。不过你需要注意，这么做的话，服务器将失去上次备份到现在所发生的
		交易。一般来说，这可以被称为回档。

		Obviously it would be retarded to use that command on a journal that is months old.....
	</s>
	<s>
		BankAccounts Collection

		This element holds all the bank accounts for a running server. Each BankAccount has a unique account number (starting from 1) and more attributes:

		* UserAccountName - The login name of the TShock account this bank account is linked to
		* WorldID - The WorldID that the account was created from, this is used when LockedToWorld is set and you want to lock bank accounts to worlds, otherwise they
		are static and are loaded in whichever world you create on the server.
		* Flags - A bit-bashed set of flags for the account that control the state of it.  Look in the source for BankAccountFlags for a definition of what the bits do.

		Please note, BankAccount elements do not keep a running total of their balance, that is done through summing all Transaction amounts
		(by XPath /Journal/Transactions/Transaction[@BankAccountFK=BankAccountK]/@Amount) linked to this account.
	</s>
	<s>
		Transaction Collection

		This element holds all the transactions for the current running server.  Each transaction is double-entry accounted,
		which means that a transaction is essentially done twice, representing the loss of money on one account, and the gain
		of money in the destination account or vice-versa.

		A double-entry account journal must have two transactions; a source and a destination, and the amounts in each must be
		the inverse of eachother: If money is to be transferred away from a source account the source amount must be negative
		and the destination amount must be positive; and conversely if money is to be transferred into a source account the
		source amount must be postitive and the destination amount must be negative.

		A Transaction has these following attributes:

		* BankAccountTransactionK - A unique number identifying this transaction
		* BankAccountFK - The unique identifier of the BankAccount element this transaction comes from
		* Amount - The amount of money this transaction was for; positive for a gain in money, negative for a loss
		* Flags - A bit-set flag of transaction options (See source for BankAccountTransferOptions for what they do)
		* Flags2 - Unused
		* BankAccountTransactionFK - A unique identifier of the opposite side of this double-entry transaction, therefore binding them together.
	</s>
	<s>[SEconomy]无法将{0}复制到{1}.</s>
	<s>[SEconomy]正在写入记录.</s>
	<s>[SEconomy]记录保存失败.</s>
	<s>[SEconomy]无法删除临时文件.</s>
	<s>[SEconomy]已备份记录.</s>
	<s>[SEconomy]发生未知错误, 请及时备份.</s>
	<s>[SEconomy]正在加载记录.</s>
	<s>加载记录.</s>
	<s>[未找到, 创建新文件]</s>
	<s>拒绝</s>
	<s>失败</s>
	<s>解压日志</s>
	<s>parsing accounts</s>
	<s>upgrading transactions</s>
	<s>[SEconomy]文件损坏.</s>
	<s>[SEconomy]发生错误, 账户和交易记录已丢失.\n\n已创建新的纪录.\n旧的记录已被移动到SEconomy.journal.xml.gz.corrupt</s>
	<s>[SEconomy]正在压缩记录.</s>
	<s>[SEconomy]重新同步在线账户.</s>
	<s>账户错误.</s>
	<s>[SEconomy]你还需要{0}才能完成本次交易.</s>
</Language>